<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Gustavo Paterno</title>
    <link>/publication/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Gustavo Paterno</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Gustavo Paterno 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/publication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Evolution of aerial spider webs coincided with repeated structural optimization of silk anchorages</title>
      <link>/publication/2019_wolff_spider_evolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/2019_wolff_spider_evolution/</guid>
      <description>Citation Wolff, J. O., Paterno, G. B., Liprandi, D., Ramírez, M. J., Bosia, F., Meijden, A., Michalik, P., Smith, H. M., Jones, B. R., Ravelo, A. M., Pugno, N., &amp;amp; Herberstein, M. E. (2019). Evolution of aerial spider webs coincided with repeated structural optimization of silk anchorages. Evolution, 73(10), 2122–2134. https://doi.org/10.1111/evo.13834</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sensiPhy: An r-package for sensitivity analysis in phylogenetic comparative methods</title>
      <link>/publication/2018_mee_paterno-et-al_sensiphy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/2018_mee_paterno-et-al_sensiphy/</guid>
      <description>Citation Paterno, G. B., Penone, C., &amp;amp; Werner, G. D. A. (2018). sensiPhy: An r-package for sensitivity analysis in phylogenetic comparative methods. Methods in Ecology and Evolution, 9(6), 1461–1467. https://doi.org/10.1111/2041-210X.12990</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Integrating ecosystem functions into restoration ecology-recent advances and future directions</title>
      <link>/publication/2016_kollmann_restoration-ecology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/2016_kollmann_restoration-ecology/</guid>
      <description>Citation Kollmann, J., Meyer, S. T., Bateman, R., Conradi, T., Gossner, M. M., de Souza Mendonça, M., … Weisser, W. W. (2016). Integrating ecosystem functions into restoration ecology-recent advances and future directions. Restoration Ecology, 24(6), 722–730. https://doi.org/10.1111/rec.12422</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Species-specific facilitation, ontogenetic shifts and consequences for plant community succession</title>
      <link>/publication/2016_jvs_paterno-et-al_facilitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/2016_jvs_paterno-et-al_facilitation/</guid>
      <description>Citation Paterno, G. B., Siqueira Filho, J. A., &amp;amp; Ganade, G. (n.d.). Species-specific facilitation, ontogenetic shifts and consequences for plant community succession. Journal of Vegetation Science, 27(3), 606–615. https://doi.org/10.1111/jvs.12382</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Background noise as a selective pressure: stream-breeding anurans call at higher frequencies</title>
      <link>/publication/2016_rhor-et-al_anura-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/2016_rhor-et-al_anura-call/</guid>
      <description>Citation Röhr, D. L., Paterno, G. B., Camurugi, F., Juncá, F. A., &amp;amp; Garda, A. A. (2016). Background noise as a selective pressure: stream-breeding anurans call at higher frequencies. Organisms Diversity and Evolution, 16(1), 269–273. https://doi.org/10.1007/s13127-015-0256-0</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public awareness of the economic potential and threats to sharks of a tropical oceanic archipelago in the western South Atlantic</title>
      <link>/publication/2016_mp_garla_shark/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/2016_mp_garla_shark/</guid>
      <description>citation Garla, R. C., Freitas, R. H. a., Calado, J. F., Paterno, G. B. C., &amp;amp; Carvalho, A. R. (2015). Public awareness of the economic potential and threats to sharks of a tropical oceanic archipelago in the western South Atlantic. Marine Policy, 60, 128–133. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.marpol.2015.06.012</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>